# DALE LINN

# Nashville, TN

Phone: 615.626.5361 | Email: dale@linn.net

LinkedIn:.linkedin.com/in/dalelinn/ | Portfolio: github.com/dlerhetal

### **SUMMARY**

Analyst with a background in business. Logical and creative problem-solver with a strong foundation in data analysis, a passion for extracting insights from complex data sets, a Data Analytics certification from Vanderbilt, and real world experience collaborating with teams to design and deliver effective results in a variety of settings.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, Javascript, HTML, VBA, SQL, NoSQL

**Applications:** GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, AWS, Flask, Command Line, Tableau, ArcGIS **Tools:** Excel, Jupyter, Colab, Pandas, Matplotlib, NumPy, PyTorch, SciPy, Scikit-learn, TensorFlow, Keras

#### **PROJECTS**

### Nashville Thursday Traffic Study | NTTS GitHub | NTTS Presentation

- We studied Nashville traffic, using the US Traffic Volume Data from 2018-2022 to examine the question, "Why has Thursday traffic become more congested?"
- I selected the topic, sourced, cleaned, and transformed the data, ensuring quality and consistency for subsequent analysis, and assisted with the graphs and charts for presentation.
- Python, Excel, PowerPoint

### Davidson County Food Deserts | Food Deserts GitHub | Food Deserts Site

- We created three overlays for a Davidson County map to visualize: income levels, food deserts, and available grocery stores. The goal is for this to be a living project that improves over time.
- I selected the topic, sourced, cleaned, and transformed shape files for the geojson census tract overlay, then referenced the geojson census files and json grocery data for the final result.
- HTML, Javascript, Python

# LLM Prompt Recovery | Prompt Recovery GitHub | Prompt Recovery Contest Site

- The goal of this ongoing competition is to recover the LLM prompt that was used to transform a given text generated by Gemma. We generate texts to train, test split our learning model and submit our predictions for evaluation. Our final model will be copied to the github on or after April 17, 2024.
- I studied to understand the contest rules, generate the training text, monitor competitor progress, meet with the team to discuss training models adaptations, and submit predictions for this project.
- Kaggle Notebook, Python

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Founder/Street Team Administrator, The Jacksonville Hub, Inc. - Jacksonville, FL (2018 - Present)

Founded a non-profit organization that tracked the needs of the poor and homeless in the lower half of Health Zone One. Identified and worked with organizations that were meeting needs while identifying service gaps. We grew to serve 300 weekly with food, laundry services, and administrative help in applying for benefits (including housing) and health services.

### Area Manager, Amazon.com - Scotland & Kansas City, 2014 - 2017

Managed teams of over 100 associates for inbound and outbound operations.

Collaborated with multidisciplinary departments, alternating shifts, and senior management to unite our team and exceed all metrics. Consistently maintained documentation in quality to meet weekly and monthly metrics, driving down the number of late customer shipments to a 20% YoY improvement.

## Tech Coach, Asurion - Nashville, TN (2013 - 2014)

Developed and implemented strategies for bridging consumer demands with business realities with a tracking tool to help our team assess situation realities and share best practices. We were the first to successfully raise team Customer Satisfaction and First Call Resolution above 95%.

# Gig Work/Career Break (2010 - 2024)

I prioritized flexibility first as the at home parent and later while launching The Jacksonville Hub, Inc.

- Team Member: Whole Foods (2023 2024)
- Steak n' Shake: General Manager (2021 2022)
- English Teacher: TAL Education Group (2018)
- Driver: Uber, Lyft, Door Dash (2017 2018)
- Default Services: HUD (2011 2013)
- Field Collections: Various (2010 2013)

### **EDUCATION**

Data Analytics Certificate, Vanderbilt, Nashville, TN
MBA, Davenport, Dearborn, MI
BS Communications, Pensacola Christian College, Pensacola, FL